Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♫ A heart that remains
unchanged through time ♫
♫ Our eternal story
that will last forever ♫
[This drama is fictional, and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
[Production guidelines were followed
when filming children and animals.]
[Episode 11] What's wrong?
Is she ignoring your messages?
No.
[I just saw your text.
[I'm going to the study room.]
She's responding to all your messages.
But it feels strange, you know?
What does?
She's not ignoring me,
but it feels like she is.
Hey, why do you think
she lied to me yesterday?
I'm sure she had good reasons.
Hey, cut her some slack.
Being too clingy will turn her off.
You'll soon crash and burn.
I guess your girlfriend
is upset again today.
Jo Mi Rae is asking
what happened yesterday.
She says she's been down all day.
What? I wonder what's going on.
I tried not to bring this up,
but did you
seriously think you looked
the coolest yesterday?
Yes, isn't that a given?
Hey, to be honest, those guys
without shirts on were quite cool.
Especially the one called Won Bin.
Wow.
Even his name was Won Bin!
You can't compete with
a guy with a name like that.
Gosh, you should've just
ripped your shirts open too.
So are you saying
that U Yeon was checking someone else out?
My girl U Yeon isn't like that.
Have you ever heard of
'Seeing something can spark desire'?
It's the only
Chinese-character idiom I know.
I haven't!
Isn't that a four-character idiom?
A four-character idiom?
Yes.
Where's U Yeon?
She left already.
What do we do now?
Without U Yeon, you'll make
excuses to go alone again.
What's going on?
Just tell me already.
I like Tae Seon.
I know.
Did you also know Tae Seon likes you?
My head tells me it's not your fault,
but I just got angry
whenever I saw your face.
Don't worry. I'd never date him.
Hey!
Seriously, Yeom Se Ra.
Do you know how infuriating it is
when you talk like that?
Pretending that nothing matters
and that you don't care what happens.
I'm swallowing my pride here.
Do you have to be so dismissive?
My dad got transferred out of town.
What?
Mom wants me to go to Germany,
but I'm not sure yet.
Part of me wants to try living with Mom,
but I also feel bad for Dad.
I haven't told Song yet,
so keep this between us for now.
Okay,
I won't say a word.
I think I should go see U Yeon.
I think something's up.
Gosh. Seriously, dude.
How in the world would you know that?
A man's intuition.
Intuition, my foot.
Oh, come on.
Since when do guys have intuition?
Men just...
Stop meddling and wait.
No, I can't do that.
If something happened, I need to know.
Gosh, I don't even want to
imagine that possibility.
What if it's really another guy?
But you said it can't be Won Bin.
You said you trust her!
It's not that.
Miss Piggy's so pretty, you know?
Do you think guys will
just leave her alone?
She doesn't say it, but there must be tons.
- Gosh, just hang up.
- Still, U Yeon
is principled, so I'm not really worried.
But what if there are pests bothering her?
I doubt it, Gi Jeong.
She's too nice.
So she hates rejecting people.
What in the world!
Is the lab closed until
the end of this week?
Yes.
Hey!
U Yeon! Are you okay?
Get away from her!
Gi Jeong.
Gi Jeong, wait.
Was it this punk?
The one that's been
making life hard for you lately?
Don't worry. I'll handle this.
But
I get why you keep following U Yeon around.
Sure.
She's gorgeous.
But she's taken.
By none other than me!
I, Nam Gi Jeong, am
Song U Yeon's boyfriend.
So scram right now!
Gi Jeong, it's not like that.
It'll be over soon. Don't worry.
Are you a college student?
If you're, go hang out
with other college students.
Stop showing off and trying
to seduce an innocent minor.
If you don't back off, I'm calling the cops.
- He's my brother!
- Hello, officer?
My biological brother!
What?
Good evening, sir.
I'm U Yeon's.
I'm Nam Gi Jeong, U Yeon's guy friend,
pretending to be her boyfriend.
U Seok, you go inside first.
I need to talk with my friend for a bit.
Have a good night, sir.
Sir, please go in.
Take care.
Wow.
I almost got into big trouble.
Your brother's glare was no joke.
I'm sorry.
But for now,
- since I said I'm your guy friend...
- Are you an idiot?
Who would believe that?
What do I do now?
Things were already
awkward between me and him.
How can I face him now?
Gosh.
Am I
that embarrassing?
What?
Why did you come?
You didn't even tell me you were coming.
Are you mad I came unannounced?
You don't like it?
No, that's not what I meant.
Why are you twisting my words?
Let's sit for a minute.
I thought something was going on with you.
You wouldn't tell me anything,
so I ended up imagining
other possibilities.
Like guys were harassing you.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
Don't just assume things from now on.
And don't act so boldly without thinking.
Okay.
And nothing's going on with me.
I'm sorry if I made you worry.
But
I forgot about tomorrow's pop quiz.
Sorry.
What?
Oh...
Nothing.
Oh, right.
I need to tell you something.
I meant to tell you yesterday.
I got scouted by an entertainment agency.
What?
They want to develop me as an actor.
I said I'd consider it.
I think I'll try it.
But
you've never been
interested in that before.
True,
but...
If she dates someone
like you, it'll get worse.
I changed my mind.
Don't worry.
It's a large, reputable
company Eun Gi knows.
Once I put my heart
into it, I'll excel for sure.
Overconfident, you'd say?
I doubt that.
What?
Nothing.
I need to go now.
Okay.
Let's part ways here.
It'll be awkward if we
meet my brother again.
See you at the meeting.
You just got back?
Yes.
- The thing is...
- Don't worry.
I won't tell Mom.
Thanks, U Seok.
I got scouted by an entertainment agency.
They want to develop me as an actor.
I should've congratulated him.
How mean.
You're really terrible, Song U Yeon.
- That's so petty.
- Yes!
- You just got back?
What happened?
Who was that guy?
Older brother.
What?
U Yeon's older brother.
No way.
Hey, you didn't get beaten up?
No.
He's so forgiving. His heart is as big as
the Pacific, Indian, and Atlantic oceans.
But why do you keep frowning?
Tell me about it.
I don't know.
Something's definitely up,
but she wouldn't tell me.
Do you think she doesn't trust me?
Wouldn't trusting you be weirder?
That's a fair point.
You punks. Seriously.
Nice!
I'm first place, right?
Where are you?
I'm in my room. Why?
I'm coming downstairs for a bit.
Do you have a death wish?
Don't you dare come in here.
Are you hiding a guy in there?
Enough. I'll come up.
Game.
Why are you whining in
the middle of the night?
- Sis.
- Do you have a death wish?
What's the problem?
U Yeon's been acting cold.
What do you mean?
She's so cold to me all of a sudden.
I can't think of any reason why.
She even stayed to watch
my photo shoot yesterday.
Were you being annoying?
No, I was totally killing it.
Then why would she be like that?
Who knows? That's why I'm frustrated too.
Something must've happened.
But she won't tell me.
I guess she doesn't want to tell you.
I don't think U Yeon
likes me as much as I like her.
But she said she likes you.
That's true,
but seeing U Yeon act like this
doesn't give me confidence.
Confidence, my foot!
Maybe it's that time of the month for her!
- What?
- Don't you remember you bothered me that day
and got beaten up?
I've got my own problems to worry about.
I'm the one who needs counseling.
It's from Brown Finger.
Next meeting's theme is retro,
which had been postponed.
You prepared costumes last time, right?
See you day after tomorrow.
How exciting.
Next meeting
I want to skip it.
Should I just not go?
But you said, 'See you at the meeting.'
That's true.
But you don't feel as comfortable
around Gi Jeong anymore?
I don't.
Even more so after talking to him today.
Because he got scouted
by an entertainment agency?
Now Gi Jeong's pursuing
a concrete goal too.
You should support him.
I know that's the right thing to do.
But it hits harder that
he's on a different playing field.
I feel like I might end
up holding Gi Jeong back
and there will be many girls who are
prettier and smarter than me around him.
I'm pathetic, don't you think?
What happened?
You left me so boldly,
only to end up back as a loser.
Song U Yeon.
You really won't tell us?
What happened that day
you went to the studio?
I think I should break up with Gi Jeong.
- What?
Gi Jeong
wants to become an actor.
An actor?
He said he wasn't interested at all.
He said an agency approached him.
They said they'd support him.
What's that got to do with breaking up?
I might hinder his future...
Do you even know how
confusing it is to hear
such unilateral decisions that people make?
And why do you assume
that you'd be a hindrance?
You could actually help him.
How could I help at all?
I can't even plan my own future...
Why do we keep going in circles?
Honestly,
you've been acting so ridiculous lately.
I know how foolish
and pathetic I may seem.
But I can't control these strong feelings.
I don't know how to stop.
It feels like there's a big hole in my head
pulling everything in, Gi Jeong.
♫ I was searching for something precious ♫
♫ If you lose what's precious ♫
♫ A heart no one understands ♫
She wouldn't tell me.
Gosh, what seriously happened?
Stop asking.
She must have good reasons.
Why did you act like that earlier?
You were acting out of
character, getting angry.
You really startled me, you know?
I think even U Yeon knows that she's
saying things out of stubbornness.
How could I agree with her?
Still, you used to say things
in a nice way, you know?
If you talk nonsense even though you know better,
it means you're asking to hit rock bottom.
That's the only way to climb back up.
Then we should help
her get back up quickly.
What?
I felt the same way
when my parents divorced.
The only reason the three of us
stayed friends all this time
is because we had you
who were like an older sister figure.
If you go to Germany,
(Watch on www.kisskh.ws to support Admin)
We'll just become goofballs
who have lost our sister.
What are you talking about?
Stop crying,
okay?
- Are you crying?
- No, I'm not.
Stop crying.
[Spirit Fingers, 12th
Meeting, Dress Code: Retro]
Mr. Kwon, one instant coffee, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Me too.
Mr. Kwon, the fax machine's broken.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Kwon, what about the coffee?
Mr. Kwon, fax!
We need to receive urgent documents.
The client's throwing a fit!
Mr. Kwon, where's my coffee?
Mr. Kwon.
Fax!
Gosh, seriously!
What's wrong with you all?
I'm sorry. What can I do?
What can you do?
You all seem really down,
so we, the older ones,
are trying to cheer you up.
I'm sorry.
Okay, shall we dance to
some '70s and '80s tunes?
- No.
I bet we'd be the only ones
end up dancing anyway.
Those helpless good-for-nothings
would just ruin the sacred disco time too.
Forget it. Let's just start croquis.
No couple poses today.
Special edition.
Is this fate's cruel joke?
Their once burning passion
now reduced to ashes.
Oh, this whirlwind of emotion
stirred by the bone-chilling wind
envelops SF.
Why did they get into a fight?
Ten-minute break!
U Yeon!
I need to use the restroom.
Based on my observation,
I don't think Gi Jeong
intended anything at first.
Hello.
Your time traveler outfit
today really suits you.
Do you really think so?
Hello.
Hi there, Baeblu.
Baeblu, you look like a time traveler too.
Hey, you look so cute.
Stop it.
Where are you going?
I need to call Mi Rae.
But it seemed like U Yeon
was avoiding Gi Jeong.
Are those youngsters
already having a lover's quarrel?
Oh dear.
Then what about those two?
They've been separated like the Red Sea
since the moment they arrived.
The water...
- Hello.
- Hey, Blue.
Wow, trying out the
department head look today?
Section chief look?
Senior staff look?
Junior staff look?
Assistant manager look.
Oh, assistant manager. Looking sharp.
- Hey, Geu Rin!
- Hello.
Wow, Geu Rin's outfit concept today
I'll head in first.
What?
Geu...
It seems like Geu Rin is
walking on thin ice around Seon Ho.
Do you know anything?
Did Geu Rin offend Seon Ho in some way?
Are you going to the restroom?
No.
Then why are you out here?
Let's go.
We need to talk.
About what?
About what? Everyone's waiting.
How many times did you
make eye contact with me today?
What? Many times, of course.
No, we never once locked eyes.
You kept looking away.
Sorry, I was distracted by other thoughts.
- What thoughts?
- What?
I'm constantly thinking about you.
What's on your mind?
What's on your mind that
you can't even look me in the eye?
Gi Jeong.
Is this about me possibly
joining an agency?
If you hate it, I won't do it.
It's no big deal.
Why does everything seem so easy for you?
- What?
- Tens of thousands of people shed
blood, sweat, and tears
to get opportunities like that.
But they come so easily to you
and you discard them just as easily.
You don't even realize
what gifts you were born with.
No, you don't even care.
You get recognition
and opportunities without even trying.
Coming from someone like you,
did you think I'd fall for that too?
Song U Yeon.
I'm sorry.
Something's bothering you.
What's wrong?
No.
Nothing's wrong.
Why won't you tell me?
How can I possibly tell you
everything that happens in my life?
You really don't trust me at all?
It's not that. That's not what I meant...
Are we even really dating?
I feel like I'll die if I don't
see you even for a day.
But you don't seem to feel the same.
I'm always the only one who feels
impatient, anxious, and worried.
Honestly,
it still feels like I'm the only one in love.
That's not true, Gi Jeong. I too...
So you like me?
Then can I verify that?
Verify how?
Gi Jeong.
♫ I'm not sure what to say ♫
♫ Even when I just look at you.
Even if our fingertips just touch ♫
♫ What if you hear my pounding heart ♫
I'm heading out first.
I can't believe that punk!
I apologize,
but I need to head out early today.
♫ You've waited so
long, I'm late, I'm sorry ♫
♫ I'm new to this, so I didn't know ♫
♫ Just because it's you,
just because I like you ♫
♫ Words can't express it ♫
♫ There's no other way ♫
♫ I've captured it all here ♫
I'm sorry about today.
It seems like we're about to wrap up,
so I'll head out first too.
My apologies.
Then I should
also get going now.
Seon Ho.
Do you want to grab a drink with me?
[Late-night Food Stall]
I doubt it, you know?
Playing dating games?
Geu Rin's not immature.
Right?
But that's how I feel.
If Seon Ho feels that way,
maybe you're partly responsible?
I did nothing wrong.
I laid my whole heart bare for him.
We even kissed so many...
How many times?
Geu Rin must feel
certain about her feelings.
That's why your doubting feels
frustrating to her, you know?
She can't literally take
her heart out and show it to you.
Wouldn't it be great if you were right?
No, I'm sure you're right. But...
- But...
- Then why can't he trust me?
I mean, other than 'I
like you' and 'I love you, '
what more can I say to prove my sincerity?
Should I promise to
pluck stars from the sky?
That's why I compensated with
more than words. All those kisses...
So how many times?
They all just felt playful.
I've known Geu Rin for seven years.
But Geu Rin
acts the same whether
we're friends or dating.
Nothing's changed.
Things should be a little different
when you're dating, don't you think?
But isn't that actually better?
If Geu Rin acts differently
when she's your girlfriend,
wouldn't that be way creepier?
You two have been friends for too long.
You probably still confuse
friendship and romance,
so that must have come
through in your actions.
Seon Ho understands,
but can't help feeling hurt.
But Seon Ho's the same way.
No.
Seon Ho was ready to be more than
friends with you whenever you were.
Was he? Why?
That's because
he's liked you for so long.
Who? Koo Seon Ho?
Hey, anyway, you ought
to understand Geu Rin.
Of course, I do.
Because I know
everything about Geu Rin.
Even more than she knows herself.
Of course. That's your
way of loving someone.
But then what's the issue?
Then
why did you suddenly snap?
He says it's because of Acaprio.
Jealousy?
It's all because of that punk, Acaprio!
Then take it out on him.
No matter how innocent you may be,
his mere existence must
be making Seon Ho upset.
You should be understanding of that.
Gosh, so heavy.
Why is she so heavy?
Am I heavy?
I've got my own private jet.
I've got a private jet.
But I can't call it right now.
It's broken.
- I'm just going to drink up!
- Gosh.
I need to fly my jet!
Seon Ho, seeing you so messed up
makes me like you more.
But
why don't you believe Geu Rin likes you?
Gosh, seriously!
Stop asking if I'm excited or not!
Please, just stop!
I'm back.
U Yeon,
you're in trouble!
What?
What's this?
Mom.
What on earth have you been doing?
Give me your phone. I'm confiscating it.
What's going on?
Mom, wait. Just hear me out first.
What's this?
Should I call this number?
[Koo Seon Ho]
What?
You went to the study room?
You acted all high and mighty
only to lie to me like this?
Why aren't you answering?
Admit your wrongdoing!
I was wrong.
Your phone.
I said, your phone!
Mom.
You're grounded from now on.
Come straight home after school.
I'll get you a tutor.
U Dol, go to your room.
What's going on?
U Seok.
What do I do about U Yeon?
Gosh, it's so frustrating.
Gosh, it's so frustrating!
Oh my, what am I going to do about U Yeon?
Oh my gosh, this is so frustrating.
Geu Rin.
Who were you drinking with on Sunday?
Seon Ho looked like he was
suffering too when I saw him earlier.
- Did you see Seon Ho?
- Yes.
He said he was exhausted
and went back to the dorm.
He wanted to rest a bit.
Did you drink with Seon Ho?
No.
Darn it, who's calling?
Hello?
It's me, Rin Rin.
How'd you get my number?
I'm blocking you.
You'll regret it.
What?
[Geu Rin]
Spit it out.
If the seniors are conversing, the juniors
ought to excuse themselves from the room.
Younger ones are so
disrespectful these days.
- Total chaos.
- I'm leaving now.
The upcoming A Midsummer Night's Dream
production has the original Broadway cast.
You know the stage director
and crew came along too, right?
- Should I?
- Of course.
That stage director was my brother's
best friend during his studies abroad.
So I begged him to pay a visit
to our school's studio theater.
Why?
Why else?
It's for you.
The pretext
is that he's advising on the
stage design for our fall production.
Does someone like that
really have nothing better to do
than advising a college play?
Geu Rin,
it's me, you know?
Heo Zero.
I can make all things possible.
[A Midsummer Night's Dream]
What do you think?
It's rare to get a chance to talk
with a stage director
from Broadway.
We're meeting at the studio theater
day after tomorrow at 6 p.m.
Come by.
I'll introduce you.
Think about it and let me know.
You got my number, right?
I'll get going.
The day after tomorrow at 6 p.m.?
Yes, 6 p.m.
He has an interesting way to agonize.
How many hours has it been?
Gi Jeong. Hey, Nam Gi Jeong!
Don't call me. You're ruining my rhythm.
Jo Mi Rae says,
do not call or text U Yeon.
Tell her I wouldn't even if she begged.
That's not what I mean.
Her mom confiscated her phone.
What?
Koo Seon Ho.
Are you feeling okay?
What?
How did you know?
Myeong Hun told me.
What's Myeong Hun doing?
He's like an owl, delivering messages.
Well, are you okay?
He said you went to rest.
How did you know?
Myeong Hun told me.
Myeong Hun's an owl indeed.
Shouldn't we talk?
Well,
why aren't you answering?
You don't want to see me?
It's not like that.
I want to see you.
Then why won't you answer?
I have so much to say to you.
Me too. I have so much to say to you too.
But not right now.
Not right now?
No.
After I wrap things up,
let's meet up then.
Fine.
I don't get it but I'll do as you wish.
Just don't take too long.
Or I'll get upset again.
Upset?
You get upset too?
I do get upset too, you know?
I'm an interesting human being too.
Okay.
Wait just a little longer.
What?
Wait.
Nam Gi Jeong?
Well...
Where's U Yeon?
She won't be coming to
the study room anymore.
Actually, she can't.
Why not?
I, Nam Gi Jeong, am
Song U Yeon's boyfriend.
So scram right now!
He's my brother!
My biological brother!
Did she find out about me?
What?
No,
her mom found out about her drawings.
- What?
- She found out U Yeon's going to SF.
Her mom tore up her
drawings and went crazy.
- What?
- She's grounded, so she can't come to study room
and has to go straight home after school.
Hey, Nam Gi Jeong.
That aside,
did something happen
between you and U Yeon?
- What?
- By any chance,
did you betray U Yeon?
No.
In any case,
if you betray Song,
I'll skin you alive!
- Thank you, sir.
- Goodbye.
- See you again, U Yeon.
- Take care.
Good night.
What?
You're home early today.
Welcome home, Dad.
Who was that?
U Yeon's tutor I told you about.
I heard he always knows
exactly what's going to be on the test.
Are you sure we're not
wasting time for nothing?
That's enough.
If tutoring were going to help,
her grades should've improved ages ago.
I've told you countless times.
Stop wasting money.
But still...
Enough!
I'm traveling next week.
Pack my things in advance.
Gosh, where to? For how long?
You heard how worried Dad is, right?
Worried?
I'm telling you this just in case.
Don't mention drawings
or whatever in front of your dad.
Got it?
U Dol, have some spinach too.
Open up.
Look at him. He's all grown up now
and doesn't want me to feed him anymore.
He's in third grade. He's all grown up.
How long are you going
to treat him like a baby?
He only looks big. He's still a baby.
He doesn't know how to
do anything besides studying.
Dad.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
Sure, later.
- U Seok, you've been at the lab lately...
- Later when?
You always say that
but never actually listen.
Dad's having an important
talk with your brother.
As for me,
I wish
you'd scold me like Mom does instead.
That would be so much better
than being treated like I'm invisible!
Why are you acting up like this at dinner?
Come on, U Yeon.
- Get up.
- Why don't you hear her out first
to find out what she has to say.
But please finish your dinner first.
Let's take some time
to talk after dinner.
Though I believed I could convince them,
part of me still feared I might fail.
So Dad's answer didn't shock me.
Because it was as expected.
What truly disappointed me
was my own pathetic self.
The moment I faced Dad's stern expression,
my heart started to race
and mind went blank.
All I managed was to
let out a few stumbling words.
No.
I won't allow it,
okay?
Consider this conversation never happened.
Why did you bring that up
knowing that it'd go nowhere?
Look at how you've ruined
the whole family's mood.
Now I have to tiptoe
around Dad because of you.
What exactly do you do at home?
What have you been
doing to make her like that?
Why are you blaming me again?
You just hang around other moms all day.
That's exactly why
she turned out like that!
What about you?
You come home only on weekends.
You never look after kids!
Then you go earn money!
If you hadn't held me back, I wouldn't have
ended up in that countryside, you hear me?
I want to die.
Gi Jeong.
Come straight home after school.
Don't keep your tutor waiting.
Okay.
U Dol! Song U Dol!
Time to wake up.
A prince shouldn't sleep
in this late, you know?
Will you get up yourself?
Or should I come in?
Can you do it on your own?
I'm coming in.
Wait.
U Dol, that's your
brother-in-law over there.
Brother-in-law.
Ice cream.
Here you go, Bong Gu.
My mom will be here soon.
You'll be in trouble
if she finds out.
Is she coming to pick you up?
It must be so tough for her.
Don't you hate my mom?
The reason U Yeon keeps you
a secret is because of her.
Because my mom has a terrible personality.
You shouldn't say that about your mom.
Moms and Dads are all like that.
They're just worried, that's all.
He's right, U Dol. What's wrong?
Why are you pretending to be nice?
My mom has a terrible personality.
She tore up U Yeon's drawings too.
That's why I came.
How's your sister?
- Is everything okay?
- She's fine.
She's just obeying my mom like an idiot.
What are you doing?
That's my number.
If anything happens to your sister,
please call me.
Promise?
I'll get going now.
I don't hate your mom,
but she scares me.
Wow, he's fast.
[Giant Creep]
He asked if you were okay.
Give him a call.
No, it's okay.
Coward.
What?
Cuckoo,
cuckoo, cuckoo.
Over here.
Cuckoo.
Hey!
U Yeon,
U Yeon!
U Seok,
what are you doing here?
What?
What's that?
Where did you get that?
It's mine.
Don't tell Mom and Dad.
What?
Let's go.
U Yeon.
I was lucky to see you today.
I still have so many
questions I want to ask you,
but I'll hold back.
It's okay if you never tell me.
You must have your reasons.
Meeting you taught me
that something like that exists.
Also,
I'm sorry for being pushy that day.
I must've been out of my mind.
I'm so embarrassed
that I can't even face you.
Like you said,
I'll keep waiting.
If you won't forgive
me until the day you die,
then I'll wait for you until the day I die.
And this
is the message I'll send when we make up.
So don't make me wait too long.
I miss you, U Yeon.
♫ I run toward you until I'm breathless ♫
♫ Even if I forget
everything, it doesn't matter ♫
♫ I'll turn coincidence into destiny ♫
♫ Now shout to the ends of the earth.
You're my destiny ♫
I'm sorry. It's all because
I was being too petty.
Something happened to your girlfriend's
family. The little one ran away from home.
Even when we were dating,
I always cared about Seon Ho more than you.
Come back to me.
I'll start fresh from that point.
- Do what you want.
- U Seok!
But do it smartly, so
that you don't get hurt.
I should do it too. Dating.
Today's main character is late.
He's not getting a buzzcut, is he?
No way.
- Bong Gu.
- Oh no, Bong Gu.
Why?
What nonsense is this?
Gi Jeong, you're right.
I
I've fallen for you.
Wait,
we're here already?
We'll see each other again tomorrow.
Let's just walk a little more
until we get to your place, okay?
Wait.
I don't want to leave.
You have to. What if we bump into my mom?
I'll greet her politely.
Hello. I'm Nam Gi Jeong.
Please entrust your daughter to me.
She'll break my legs in two.
This isn't the Joseon era, you know?
She'll say, 'Your grades are bad.
You have no time for dating.'
I want to grow up fast and rescue you.
Just go already.
Do you really have to go in right now?
I think being 20 minutes
late should be okay.
All right!